okay these are constant tension need
magnet bar those new pages but it works
better when you have a free water
bottles at Zeitoun because you can see
the places don't touch the ground I've
got a plus punch here to protect the
hitch so there's no pain there were no
gluten division and then this is a
medium slingshot big circle and some
people wonder what was the point of it
well if she relaxes it both her knees in
word if carrier pushes out she's going
to use the glue to breathe hip abduction
or to keep the banjo otherwise medieval
period so relaxed so she's going to push
the knees out and pull that they're not
a whole step while helping out 30 glute
bridges but sometimes people supply
chakras during the set that's what I'm
going to stand right here against Karen
to share this slide not possess so
anyway this is her third assessment unit
in three sets of 30 reps when eighty
seven and a medium fan in mystical if
you know I would certainly just use
maybe banner you can double up many
guarantees people one year and one
Maloney's lots of options if you don't
have a pre-loaded bubble you still
though cuz they don't work as well to
keep up to you the bardo uses
Holland place like 10 10 complex as you
can
anyway give them to dryer burns like
crazy here's what it looks like
one two three four five six eight nine